Guide to the Cornell University Cooperative Extension records, 1915-2009.
Cornell University Cooperative Extension records, 1915-2009.
- Series I. Subject Files
  - Northeast Extension Directors'-Meetings, Reports, Conferences, 1999-2001 (Box 75, Folder 28)
  - Northeast Extension Directors' Meetings, 2001 (Box 75, Folder 29)
  - Cornell Cooperative Extension Educators, 2001 (Box 75, Folder 30)
  - Vision Statements, 1999-2001 (Box 75, Folder 31)
  - Organizational Charts, 2000-2006, 2008 (Box 75, Folder 32)
  - Extension Trends and Goals
  - Department of Information and Extension Education, 1945 (Box 82, Folder 34)
  - Onondaga-Office of Price Administration Incident, 1945 (Box 82, Folder 35)
  - Marketing, 1954-1960 (Box 82, Folder 36)
  - Marketing-Poultry, 1953-1954 (Box 82, Folder 37)
  - Marketing-Vegetables, 1954-1955 (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Marketing, 1954-1959 (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Marketing Objectives, 1955 (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Marketing-Rochester, 1955-1957 (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Marketing Objectives-Handlers or Firms, 1956 (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Resolutions and Recommendations by Participants in Marketing Regional Training School, 1956 (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - National Extension Marketing Committee-Minutes and Objectives, 1956 (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Marketing Advisory Committee-Hudson Valley, 1956-1957 (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Marketing Agents-Administration, 1956-1958 (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Marketing Agents Training, 1956-1959 (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - An Evaluation of the Organization and Procedures in Conducting Extension Marketing Programs, 1957-1958 (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Extension Administration-Marketing Organization, 1958 (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - Marketing, 1960 (Box 83, Folder 13)
  - Extension Marketing Project, 1961 (Box 83, Folder 14)
  - National Marketing Workshop, Chicago, 1959-04 (Box 82, Folder 38)
  - Plane Report, 1973-1976 (Box 75, Folder 34)
  - Trends and Goals, 1974-1984 (Box 75, Folder 35)
  - Situation/Trend/Outlook Statements, 1988-1991 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Commission on the Future of Cornell Cooperative Extension-Meetings, 1986 (Box 75, Folder 36)
  - Commission on the Future of Cornell Cooperative Extension, 1986-1987 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - Commission on the Future of Cornell Cooperative Extension, 1986-1990 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Future of Cornell Cooperative Extension-Fleming Report, 1987-1998 (Box 76, Folder 3)
  - Future of the Cornell Cooperative Extension, 1998,2002 (Box 76, Folder 4)
  - Strategic Directions, 1995-1996 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Strategic Plan-Marketing, 2000-2004 (Box 76, Folder 5)
  - Peer Review Report of Economics Development Administration University Center, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - Committed to Excellence, 1998-2003 (Box 76, Folder 7)
  - Marketing Strategies, 1975-2011 (Box 89, Folder 10)
  - Farm Bureau and Extension Services
  - Publications concerning Farm Bureaus and Extension, 1913-1939 (Box 79, Folder 1)
  - Publications concerning Farm Bureaus and Extension, 1917-1959 (Box 80)
  - Federal Training Schools, 1916-1918 (Box 79, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence concerning Extension and Rural Electrification, 1918-1946 (Box 79, Folder 3)
  - Farm Bureau Charts-L.R. Simons (Box 79, Folder 4)
  - Farm Bureau-Annual Meetings, Committees, Conferences, 1920-1929 (Box 79, Folder 5)
  - C.B. Smith Papers-Federal Extension Service, 1920-1939 (Box 79, Folder 17)
  - Farm Bureau-County Analysis-L.R.Simons, 1921-1922 (Box 79, Folder 6)
  - Farm Bureau-County Analysis Summaries-L.R.Simons, 1923-1924 (Box 79, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence concerning the Extension Bulletin: "The Farm Bureau Community Committee and Program of Work, 1923 (Box 79, Folder 8)
  - Report of Corn Borer Campaign, 1927 (Box 79, Folder 9)
  - Farm Bureau Organization Suggestions, 1929 (Box 80, Folder 3)
  - Farm Bureau Organization Suggestions, 1931-1932 (Box 79, Folder 10)
  - Farm Bureau Organization Suggestions, 1932 (Box 80, Folder 4)
  - A Demonstration in County Development-Tompkins County, 1930-1939 (Box 79, Folder 11)
  - Human Problems in County Agent Work, 1932 (Box 79, Folder 12)
  - "Electric Power for the Farmer" by M.C. Burritt, 1936 (Box 79, Folder 13)
  - Grange-Farm Bureau-Extension Relations, 1941-1950 (Box 81, Folder 28)
  - World War II-Streamlining the Extension Service, 1942 (Box 79, Folder 14)
  - County Extension Agents Relations with Farm and Home Bureaus, 1943 (Box 81, Folder 29)
  - Relations with Farm and Home Bureaus, 1943 (Box 81, Folder 30)
  - Relations of Extension Service and Farm Organizations, 1943-1947 (Box 81, Folder 31)
  - American Farm Bureau Federation-Summary of State Laws, 1943-1948 (Box 80, Folder 5)
  - Coordination of Agricultural Programs and their Administration (Prepared by the American Farm Bureau Federation), 1947-1948 (Box 81, Folder 32)
  - History of Farm Bureau, 1950-1959 (Box 81, Folder 33)
  - Farm Bureau's Evolution of Fifty Years-E.S. Foster (Box 79, Folder 15)
  - Extension Study Committee (Box 79, Folder 16)
  - Talks by L.R.Simons, 1917-1963 (Box 79, Folder 18)
  - Talks by L.R.Simons, 1917-1963 (Box 79, Folder 19)
  - Talks by L.R.Simons, 1917-1963 (Box 79, Folder 20)
  - Talks by L.R.Simons-The Relation of the Farm Bureau, 1920 (Box 79, Folder 21)
  - Talks by L.R.Simons, 1920-1929 (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - Talks by L.R.Simons, 1929-1931 (Box 79, Folder 23)
  - Talks by L.R.Simons, 1932-1933 (Box 79, Folder 24)
  - Talks by L.R.Simons, 1934 (Box 79, Folder 25)
  - Talks by L.R.Simons, 1935 (Box 79, Folder 26)
  - Talks by L.R.Simons, 1936-1937 (Box 79, Folder 27)
  - Talks by L.R.Simons, 1938-1939 (Box 79, Folder 28)
  - Talk by L.R.Simons-"Twenty Years of Cooperation Between the Farm Bureau and the Extension Service-includes a photograph, 1938 (Box 79, Folder 29)
  - "Events Leading up to the Organization of the American Farm Bureau Federation-L.R.Simons, 1939 (Box 79, Folder 30)
  - Talks by L.R.Simons, 1940-1942 (Box 79, Folder 31)
  - Talks by L.R.Simons, 1943-1944 (Box 79, Folder 32)
  - Talks by L.R.Simons, 1945-1946 (Box 79, Folder 33)
  - Talks by L.R.Simons, 1947 (Box 79, Folder 34)
  - Talks by L.R.Simons, 1948-1950 (Box 79, Folder 35)
  - Talks by L.R.Simons, 1951-1953 (Box 79, Folder 36)
  - Talks by L.R.Simons, 1954 (Box 79, Folder 37)
  - Legislative
  - Smith Lever Funding, 1913-1992 (Box 76, Folder 8)
  - Smith Lever Act-Amendment, 1962 (Box 76, Folder 9)
  - Memorandum on Suggested Program of Work with Young People on New York Farms by the Department of Agricultural Economics (Box 81, Folder 34)
  - Memoranda of Agreement, 1920-1939 (Box 81, Folder 35)
  - Laws of New York-Chapter 505-Relative to Vocational Education and Extension Boards in Counties, 1926 (Box 76, Folder 10)
  - Supreme Court Decision-Monroe County, New York, 1932 (Box 76, Folder 11)
  - Supreme Court Decision-Agricultural Adjustment Act, 1935-1952 (Box 81, Folder 36)
  - Soil Conservation and Domestic Allotment Act, 1936 (Box 81, Folder 37)
  - Agricultural Adjustment Law (1937)and Soil Conservation Districts Law (1945), 1937;1945 (Box 81, Folder 38)
  - Federal Social Security Act, 1937 (Box 81, Folder 39)
  - Food Stamp Plan, 1939 (Box 81, Folder 40)
  - Hatch Act-Political Activity, 1940-1944 (Box 81, Folder 41-42)
  - Legislation-Various Bills, 1941-1957 (Box 81, Folder 43)
  - Soil Conservation Districts Law, 1946 (Box 81, Folder 44)
  - Association of Land-Grant Colleges and Universities-Revised Constitution and By-laws, 1946 (Box 81, Folder 45)
  - Agricultural Coordination and Lon-Range Policy, 1947 (Box 81, Folder 46)
  - Wildlife Conservation Bill, 1947 (Box 81, Folder 47)
  - Drainage Legislation, 1948-1949 (Box 81, Folder 48)
  - Federal, State, Local Relations in Agriculture, 1949 (Box 81, Folder 49)
  - Memorandum Regarding Relations of Ornamentals Research Laboratory, Farmingdale, New York and Extension Service and Departments of Floriculture, Plant Pathology and Entomology, 1949 (Box 81, Folder 50)
  - Granger Bill-Statement prepared by L.R. Simons, 1950 (Box 81, Folder 51)
  - Drought and Disaster, 1952-1957 (Box 81, Folder 52)
  - Congressman Hope-To Cooperate with State and Local Agencies in the Planning and Carrying out of Works of Improvement for Soil Conservation and Other Purposes, 1953 (Box 81, Folder 53)
  - Memorandum of Understanding-Soil Conservation Service, 1953 (Box 81, Folder 54)
  - Consolidated Extension Act-Approved, 1953-06 (Box 76, Folder 12)
  - Agricultural Extension Service-Policy regarding Relationships with Cooperatives, 1954-1955 (Box 81, Folder 13)
  - Cooperative Corporations Laws, 1954 (Box 82, Folder 1)
  - Memorandum No. 1368-Secretary, U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1954-1955 (Box 82, Folder 2)
  - Memorandum of Understanding between Cornell and the U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1955-02 (Box 82, Folder 3)
  - Soil Bank Program- Public Law 540, 1956 (Box 82, Folder 4)
  - Study of Organization and Procedural Patterns in Office of State Leader of Home Demonstration Agents, 1956 (Box 76, Folder 13)
  - General Extension-Agricultural Extension-Legislation, 1956-1959 (Box 82, Folder 5)
  - New York City State Law, 1957 (Box 76, Folder 14)
  - Cooperative Agreement between the Interdepartmental Committee on Low Incomes, the State of New York and the New York State College of Agriculture, 1958 (Box 82, Folder 6)
  - Fish and Wildlife Management Act and the Extension Service, 1958-1961 (Box 82, Folder 7)
  - The Extension Service Partnership in New York State, L.R. Simons, 1960 (Box 82, Folder 8)
  - Donated Commodities, 1961-1973 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Omnibus Farm Bill, 1961 (Box 82, Folder 9)
  - Food and Agriculture Act of 1962 (Box 82, Folder 10)
  - Food Stamp Program, 1965-1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Taylor Act, 1967-1969 (Box 76, Folder 15)
  - County Law Section 224-Correspondence, 1983-1992 (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - County Law Section 224-Correspondence, 1993 (Box 76, Folder 17)
  - County Law Section 224-Correspondence, 1994-1998 (Box 76, Folder 18)
  - New York State Laws-pending-Correspondence, 1989-1998 (Box 76, Folder 19)
  - Legal Counsel, 1991-1992 (Box 76, Folder 20)
  - Legislators-Correspondence, 1990-1999 (Box 76, Folder 21)
  - Legislators-Correspondence, 1990-1999 (Box 76, Folder 22)
  - Legislators-Correspondence, 1985-1992 (Box 76, Folder 23)
  - Legislators-Correspondence, 1993-2000 (Box 76, Folder 24)
  - Legislators-Correspondence, 194-2000 (Box 76, Folder 25)
  - Political Support for Extension, 1990-1999 (Box 76, Folder 26)
  - Honorable Amory Houghton, 1995-1998 (Box 76, Folder 27)
  - State Budget Requests, 1995-1999 (Box 76, Folder 28)
  - Survey-New York State-Bill Lacy, 1995-1999 (Box 76, Folder 29)
  - Cornell Legislative Reception, 1997 (Box 76, Folder 30)
  - Soil and Water Conservation
  - Extension's Part in Soil Conservation-L.D. Kelsey, 1933-1958 (Box 82, Folder 11)
  - New York State Soil Conservation Districts Laws, 1936 (Box 80, Folder 18)
  - Soil Conservation Districts Association, 1936-1955 (Box 82, Folder 12)
  - Soil and Water Conservation Research Needs, 1937-1955 (Box 82, Folder 13)
  - Soil and Water Conservation Research Needs, 1956-1960 (Box 82, Folder 14)
  - State Soil Conservation Committee, 1940-1960 (Box 82, Folder 15)
  - Soils and Soil Associations of New York, 1949-1955 (Box 82, Folder 16)
  - New York State Soil Conservation Committee-Minutes of Meetings, 1952-1961 (Box 80, Folder 19)
  - Extension-Soil Conservation Service Reorganization, 1953-1954 (Box 82, Folder 17)
  - Water Resources and Development, 1954-1961 (Box 82, Folder 18)
  - Soil Testing-GLF Extension, 1955-1958 (Box 82, Folder 19)
  - New York State Soil Conservation Public Law 566, 1955-1959 (Box 80, Folder 20)
  - Soil Conservation Districts Association, 1956-1962 (Box 82, Folder 20)
  - Water Policies for Eastern Agriculture-Charles C. Butler, 1958-10 (Box 82, Folder 21)
  - Regional Research Center-Soil and Water Resources, 1958-1960 (Box 82, Folder 22)
  - University
  - Proposed Plan for Further Developing the Graduate Program in Extension Education at Cornell-Report of Leagan's Committee, 1952 (Box 82, Folder 23)
  - Evaluation of the Colleges of Agriculture and Home Economics-by the Middle States Association, 1957 (Box 82, Folder 24)
  - Graduate Course for Resources Management or Natural Resources Development, 1958-1958 (Box 82, Folder 25)
  - American Indian Program, 1988-2000 (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Biotechnology Program, 1990-1999 (Box 77, Folder 2)
  - City and Regional Planning, 1997-1999 (Box 77, Folder 3)
  - Cornell Center for the Environment and Cornell Laboratory for Environmental Applications for Remote Sensing (CLEARS), 1988-2000 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Cornell Center for the Environment, 1990-1994 (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Center for the Environment, 1994-2001 (Box 77, Folder 6)
  - Cornell Cooperative Extension Week, 1995-1999 (Box 89, Folder 5)
  - Cornell Institute for Biology Teachers, 1992-1994 (Box 77, Folder 7)
  - Cornell International Institute for Food, Agriculture and Development, 1989-2001 (Box 77, Folder 8)
  - Cornell International Institute for Food, Agriculture and Development-External Program Review, 2000 (Box 77, Folder 9)
  - Cornell Office for Tech Access and Business Assistance (COTABA), 1996 (Box 77, Folder 10)
  - Cornell Outreach Council, 1994-2000 (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Department of Communication Arts-Review-Broadhead Report, 1974 (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Local Government Program, 1996-1997 (Box 77, Folder 13)
  - Office of Distance Learning, 1995-1998 (Box 77, Folder 14)
  - Office of Distance Learning, 1999-2005 (Box 77, Folder 15)
  - Office of Government Affairs/Albany Regional Office, 1987-2003 (Box 77, Folder 16)
  - U.S.D.A.
  - Realized Cost of Agricultural and Related Programs, 1932-1954 (Box 82, Folder 26)
  - Memorandum of Understanding Between the New York State College Agricultural Extension Service and the Soil Conservation Service of the USDA, 1935 (Box 82, Folder 27)
  - Activities by Department Officers (U.S.D.A.)and Employees with Relation to General Farm Organizations, 1941 (Box 82, Folder 28)
  - "What Agricultural Extension Is"- C.B. Smith, 1932-1954 (Box 82, Folder 29)
  - An Analysis of the Sources of Cooperative Extension Funds- H.W. Gilbertson, Technical Analyst, U.S.D.A., 1948-1949 (Box 82, Folder 30)
  - Federal Extension Service-Charts Showing Appropriations, Expenditures, 1940-1979 (Box 82, Folder 31)
  - Civil Defense Information-U.S.D.A., 1950-1960 (Box 82, Folder 31A)
  - U.S.D.A. Memoranda Nos. 1278, 1279, 1280, 1951 (Box 82, Folder 32)
  - U.S.D.A. Advisory Committees, 1956 (Box 82, Folder 33)
  - USDA/CSREES - Annual Report, 1997 (Box 89, Folder 1)
- Series II. Awards and Biographical Material
  - Biographical Files-Faculty and Staff-A-B, 1930-1969 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - Biographical Files-Faculty and Staff-E-K, 1930-1969 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Biographical Files-Faculty and Staff-M, 1930-1969 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Biographical Files-Faculty and Staff-N-P, 1930-1969 (Box 72, Folder 4)
  - Biographical Files-Faculty and Staff-R-S, 1930-1969 (Box 72, Folder 5)
  - Biographical Files-Faculty and Staff-S-U, 1930-1969 (Box 72, Folder 6)
  - Biographical Files-Faculty and Staff-V, X, Z, 1930-1969 (Box 72, Folder 7)
  - Biographical Files-Faculty and Staff-W, 1930-1969 (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - U.S.D.A. Honor Awards, 1947-1963 (Box 85, Folder 22)
  - Extension Recognition Award, 1992-1997 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - Friends of Extension Award, 1992-2004 (Box 73, Folder 2)
  - Extension Outreach Award, 1997-1998 (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Proclamations from Governor Pataki - Recognizing Cornell Cooperative Extension, 1995-1999 (Box 89)
- Series III. Publications
  - Cornell Publications
    - Ellen Richard's Creed (Box 47, Folder 1)
    - Eleven cards pertaining to the preparation and preservation of food and fireless cookers, published by Cooperative Agricultural Extension Work in cooperation with the New York State Food Supply Commission., 1915-1927 (Box 47, Folder 1A)
    - Information Management in Program Planning and Evaluation (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Food Marketing Handbook-Cereals and Breads, Dairy Products, Fish, 1953-1964 (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - Food Marketing Handbook-Fruits and Nuts, 1954-1964 (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Food Marketing Handbook-Meats, 1959-1960 (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Food Marketing Handbook-Poultry and Eggs, Fats and Oils, Sugars and Sweets, 1954-1960 (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Food Marketing Handbook-Vegetables, 1954-1965 (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Food Marketing Handbook-Vegetables and General, 1955-1959 (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Handbook for Executive Committee Members of County Extension Service Associations, 1963 (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Guide for County Extension Agents, 1960-1969 (Box 58, Folder 19)
    - Guide for Program Leaders to Develop Effective Program Committees in Cooperative Extension Associations, 1976-1980 (Box 58, Folder 20)
    - Handbook for Program Committee Members of Cooperative Extension Association, 1980 (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - Cornell 4-H Veg-News (Box 58, Folder 23)
    - Demonstration Agent-Paper by Rhoda Mekeal-"Home Economics in a Rural-Urban County", 1964 (Box 58, Folder 27)
    - 4-H Whole Grains (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Food Combos- Nutrition Education Project (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - "Home Economics Work with Low-Income People" by Marian Kira and Frank Alexander, 1961-07-01-1967-06-30 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - County Extension Recipe Booklets-including some EFNEP, 1960-1979 (Box 86, Folder 32-34)
    - Extension Booklets on various topics, including some in Spanish, 1969-1990 (Box 86, Folder 35)
    - Extension Publications from various Cooperative Extension County Associations, 1960-1999 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - The Role of the Cooperative Extension Service in New York State-Changing and Adjusting Agriculture, 1963-07 (Box 77, Folder 32)
    - Background Information on an Organization Plan for Cornell Cooperative Extension in New York State, 1964 (Box 49, Folder 42)
    - A Plan for Change in New York State, Cornell Cooperative Extension Service, 1965 (Box 49, Folder 43)
    - Consumer Clues and Cues, Undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - You Can Make and Use Puppets to Tell a Nutrition Story, Undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Penny Snitcher Series, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Home Economics Work With Low Income People, 1969 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - County Agents in Vietnam, 1969 (Box 49, Folder 44)
    - Nutrition Pamphlets in Spanish, 1969-1979 (Box 85, Folder 37)
    - Food for the Family, 1970-1981 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Food for Health, 1970-1999 (Box 85, Folder 38)
    - Iron, 1970-1989 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - War on Poverty - Twenty-four Skirmishes, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Cooperative Extension in New York State, 1971 (Box 49, Folder 45)
    - Working with Young Children- Jennifer Birckmayer, 1971 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - "The Story of Henry J. Whodoesn'tknowhatoeat" by Karen Fimbel, 1971-04 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Cooperative Extension in New York State, 1971-06 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - Cornell 4-H Veg-News, 1972-1975 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Cooperative Extension Organizational Chart, 1975 (Box 49, Folder 46)
    - CCE- Comprehensive Plan, 1975 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Snacks, 1975-1983 (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Selected Nutrition Education Teaching Materials - Sue Travis, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Safety in the Kitchen, 1970-1979 (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Calories: Food and Activity, 1970-1979 (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - Calories: Food and Activity (Spanish), 1970-1979 (Box 85, Folder 39)
    - Food Preservation Pamphlets, 1970-1989 (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - E-Communication Aids-Basic Oral, Visual and Written Communication, 1970-1989 (Box 77, Folder 33)
    - Nutrition pamphlets in various languages, 1976-1986 (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - Family Day Care - By Natalie Crowe and Barbara Pine, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Chuck Wagon, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Urban Gardening Program, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - Urban Gardening Program, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - Program Directions for Cooperative Extension, 1977 (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Growing Hope, 1977 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Local Child Advocacy Systems- by Wendy Wallitt, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Good Eating in the Backyard and Beyond- by Mary Ellen Downing, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Be a Better Shopper- Heniz Biesdorf, Mary Ellen Burris, Jo Swanson- Leader's Guide, Record Sheets, 1979 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Pro-Dairy-New York Dairy Farm Profitability and Productivity Project, 1980-1989 (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - Keeping Food Safe to Eat, 1980-1989 (Box 66, Folder 24A)
    - Sodium Food Health, 1980-1989 (Box 1, Folder 26)
    - Community Issues in the 1980's and Beyond (Box 49, Folder 19)
    - The Casowasco Conference on Cooperative Extension in Urban Areas, 1980 (Box 47, Folder 6)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension into the 80's, 1981 (Box 49, Folder 49)
    - Safe Food Preparation: It's in Your Hands!, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 27)
    - Home Economics: The Third Generation, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - Making the Most of the Eighties, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 8)
    - Marketing Cooperative Extension, 1982 (Box 47, Folder 8A)
    - Extension Home Economics Study: The Role of Information in Program Development, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Information Management in Program Planning and Evaluation, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - The Role of Information in Cooperative Extension Home Economics Program Development, 1984 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - NYLEAN - New York Learning About Eating, Activity and Nutrition, 1985-09 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - NYLEAN - New York Learning About Eating, Activity and Nutrition, 1987-07 (Box 1, Folder 30)
    - Community Issues in the 1980's and Beyond, 1984 (Box 49, Folder 50)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension Programs, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 52)
    - Using Computer Technology in Extension Programs, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 53)
    - At Risk Farm Families, 1985 (Box 49, Folder 54)
    - Information: Use With Care, 1985 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Egg Carton Nutrition - Self-Teaching Exercise, Undated (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension Work in Metropolitan Areas, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 13)
      Also in Box 42
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension International Development Education "Toward 2000: Thinking Globally- A Process for Acting Locally.", 1986 (Box 49, Folder 55)
    - Picture and Article of Governor Cuomo at State Fair with Cornell Cooperative Extension hat on head, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 56)
    - Generating the 1988-1991 Plan of Work, 1986 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Ready...Set...Retire, 1987 (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - Cornell Cooperative Extension- Helping You Put Knowledge to Work, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Program Resources, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Report of the Ad Hoc Committee on Staffing for the Cornell Cooperative Extension, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Report of the Commission: Future of the Cornell Cooperative Extension System, 1987 (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Extension in Transition Bridging the Gap, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 23)
    - Facts about Cornell Cooperative Extension: Extension Meeting with Farm Bureau Education Committee, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 25)
    - Extension in Transition Bridging the Gap, 1987 (Box 49, Folder 26)
    - Modernizing the Cornell Cooperative Extension System, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 27)
    - Cooperative Extension System National Initiatives, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 29)
    - Addressing Current Issues (brochure), 1988 (Box 49, Folder 30)
    - The State of the Extension Administration, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 34)
    - Facts about Cornell Cooperative Extension and Research: College of Agriculture and Life Sciences Orientation and Luncheon; New Faculty Orientation Luncheon, 1988 (Box 49, Folder 35)
    - Selecting Sports Equipment brochures, 1988 (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - Career Opportunities in Cornell Cooperative Extension, 1988 (Box 47, Folder 19)